Southwest Folklore Center Sound Disc Collection, 1945-1987
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 13: Norteño acordeon, Part 3: South Texas and Monterey N.L., the 1940's and 50's, Norteño acordeon, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; Quiero verte (Pedro Ayala) -- El delfo (Los Hermanos Cardenas) -- Saludamos a Texas (Narciso Martinez) -- Es mi orgullo -- El vacal (Antonio Tanguma) -- Oro blanco (Los Hermanos Cardenas) -- Caballo Bayo (Los Alegres de Teran) -- Las Gallinitas (Los Populares de China) -- Arma blanca (Jose Gonzales) -- Los Gorriones de topo chico -- Todo mi alma (Conjuntos Hermanos Banda) -- Benedicion de dios (Los Donnenos) -- A totonilco (Tony de la Rosa) -- Porque me abandonas (Agapitio Zuniga) -- La Primavera (Juan Lopez) -- Sentimienta y rencor (Conjunta Bernal) -- El Adolorido (Ruben Vela) --; SWF 88.7/D.21 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 14: The Chicano experience, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; El registro de 1918 (P.D.)(Ramirez y Sanchez) -- Radios y chicanos (Roca y Amador) -- El bootlegger (Roca y Amador) -- Consejo's al maje (Los Madrugadores) -- Se a cabo el W.P.A. (Los Madrugadores) -- Cabrestea o se ahorca (Netty y Jesus Rodriguez) -- Corrido de Europa (Garzes y Cantu) -- La discriminacion (Gaytan y Cantu) -- El Pachuco y el Tarzan (Lalo Guerrero) -- Los Piscadores (Trio San Antonio) -- Marijuana Boogie (Lalo Guerrero) -- El Mojado (Los Hermanos Barron) --; SWF 88.7/D.22 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 15: Lydia Mendoza, Part 1: First recordings, 1928-1938, Mendoza, Lydia, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; Performed by Lydia Mendoza, vocal and 12-string; Francisco Mendoza, vocal; Leonor Mendoza, vocal and guitar; Francisca Mendoza, triangle; and Maria Mendoza, mandolin... Mal hombre -- Al pie de to reja -- Los besos de mi negra -- Munda enganoso -- Sigue adelante -- El liro -- La costenita -- Las cuatro milpas -- Monterrey -- La China -- Ojitos de mi chata -- A orillas de una fuente -- El hijo prodigo -- El coco --; SWF 88.7/D.23 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 16: Lydia Mendoza, Part 2: Early recordings from the 1930's, Mendoza, Lydia, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; Performed by Lydia Mendoza, vocal and 12-string; Leonor Mendoza, lead vocals and guitar; Maria Mendoza, mandolin and vocals... Pajarito herido -- Palida luna -- Sola -- Tu portida -- Nunca -- La boda negra -- Tudiras -- Tengo a mi Lupe -- Cuatro vicios -- Noche tenebrosa y fria -- Una noche serena y obscura -- Tu ya no soplas -- En tampico esta lloriendo -- Margarita, margarita --; SWF 88.7/D.24 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 17: The First women duets, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; La Marihuana (Trio Garnica-Ascencio) -- Federico el Pelao (Lydia and Leonora Mendoza) -- A borrezco la vida (Lydia and Leonora Mendoza) -- La Guia (Juanita and Manuel Mendoza) -- Que rayos (Hermanos Padilla) -- Me gusta cantarle al viente (Hermanos Padilla) -- Suerte ingrata (Carmen y Laura) -- Los Pachucos (Juanita y Maria Mendoza) -- No volvere (Juanita y Maria Mendoza) -- El guero polvos (Juanita y Maria Mendoza) -- Vale mas que te alejes (Juanita y Maria Mendoza) -- El Cigarilla (Hermanas Huerta) -- Desdichada de ti (Lydia and Maria Mendoza) --; SWF 88.7/D.25 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 18: Los Madrugadores, Los Madrugadores, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; Ahora si date gusto vida mia -- Pido a mi novia -- El Fronterizo -- El Repatriado -- Vuela suspiro -- Ayer nacio una flor -- Maria -- Mujer del 36 -- Suenos de oro -- Dos seres que se aman -- Sonora querida -- Corrido de los temblores -- La Vida infausta -- La Balbinita -- La Voz de mi madre -- Movenita encanta dora --; SWF 88.7/D.26 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 19: Los Hermanos Chavarria, Los Hermanos Chavarria, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; Yo quisiera decirte -- Porque me obligas que te olvide -- La Tragedia de Amado Garza -- El Corrido de Laredo -- Herminia -- El Presidario -- Quiero que sepas -- Por vida de dios -- Ando en busca de una blanco palomita -- El Corrido de luz arcos -- Las Gaviotas -- Carita de virgen -- A mi Julia --; SWF 88.7/D.27 (12in.)
- Texas-Mexican border music, Vol. 24: The Texas-Mexican conjunto, Folklyric Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; La bella Italia (Bruno Villareal) -- La Baranca (Narciso Martinez) -- Sal si puedes (Santiago Jimenez) -- Amor en la playa (Pedro Anaya) -- Fiches blancas (Pedro Anaya) -- Tu condena (Los Alegres de Teran) -- La Chancla (Valerio Longoria) -- La dudo (Valerio Longoria) -- Atotonilco (Tony de la Rosa) -- La Quebrada (Ruben Vela) -- Mi unica camina (Conjunte Bernal) -- Donde estan (Los Relampagos) -- Cobardemente (Los Relampagos) -- Para despedida (Conjunto Bernal) --; SWF 88.7/D.28 (12in.)
- Slim Critchlow cowboy songs: The Crooked trail to Holbrook, Critchlow, Slim, Arhoolie Records; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; The Crooked trail to Holbrook -- Borax Bill -- The trail to Mexico -- Forty a month and found -- The Brazos River -- D-Bar-2 horse wrangler -- Windy Bill -- Goodbye old paint -- Bucking bronco -- I'd like to be in Texas -- The Buffalo skinners -- The Cowboy's lament -- Wild buckaroo -- Snag tooth Sal -- The Trusty lariat -- John Garner's trailhead -- Whiskey Bill -- The Last wagon --; SWF 88.8/D.1 (12in.)
- An Evening with Rev. Louis Overstreet, Overstreet, Rev. Louis, 1962; Arhoolie Records; Recorded at St. Luke Powerhouse Church of God in Christ, Phoenix, AZ, 1962; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; A prayer -- I'm a soldier in the army of the Lord -- Workin' on the building -- Yeah, Lord -- Getting richer -- Is there anybody there -- Holiness dance --; SWF 88.9/D.1 (12in.)
- Down from the mountain, Bronson, Stan with Kathy, Arliene, and Mary, Blanding, UT., Bronson and Cooper Records; Recorded by Audio Recorders of Arizona, Phoenix, AZ.; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Down from the mountain -- Haskel -- Adios amigo -- Blue mountain -- Border of the City -- Song of White Mesa -- Friendship -- Man to man -- Posey --; SWF 89.2/D.1 (12in.)
- Down from the mountain, Bronson, Stan with Kathy, Arliene, and Mary, Blanding, UT., Bronson and Cooper Records; Recorded by Audio Recorders of Arizona, Phoenix, AZ.; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Down from the mountain -- Haskel -- Adios amigo -- Blue mountain -- Border of the City -- Song of White Mesa -- Friendship -- Man to man -- Posey --; SWF 89.2/D.1 (12in.)
- The Chambers out West, The Chambers, 1987; Tucson, AZ., Bunkhouse Productions, p1987; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Whoopi ti yi yo -- Pecos Bill -- Home on the range -- Golden slippers -- Echo of an old man's last ride -- San Antonio Rose -- Why Wyoming -- Columbus stockade blues -- Tumbling tumbleweeds -- Vaya con dios --; SWF 89.6/D.1 (12in.)
- At the rodeo again -- Life of rodeo cowboy, The Thunders, 1980; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1980; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by The Thunders... Leonard Yazzie, bass; Gary Yazzie, drums and vocals; Henry Wauneka (lead and rhythm guitar) -- At the rodeo again -- Life of rodeo cowboy --; SWF 89.24/D.1 (7in.)
- Basket dance -- Round dance, Natay, Edward Lee, Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 10 in.; Performed by Edward Lee Natay... Round dance (Kiowa - Oklahoma) -- Basket dance (Hopi - Arizona) --; SWF 89.24/D.2 (10in.)
- The Train to Gallup -- Goodnight, ladies, Mesa Verde National Park Team, Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 10 in.; Performed by Mesa Verde National Park Team with drum... The train to Gallup (Navajo) -- Goodnight Ladies (Navajo) --; SWF 89.24/D.3 (10in.)
- In-law -- My cute little Eskimo, Begay, Reg, Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 10 in.; Performed by Reg Begay with group singers... In-law (Navajo maypole dance song) -- My cute little Eskimo (Navajo skip dance song) --; SWF 89.24/D.4 (10in.)
- Navajo squaw dance -- Song of the sky city, Natay, Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 10 in.; Performed by Edward Lee Natay... With drum and rattle... Navajo squaw dance -- Sonmg of the sky city --; SWF 89.24/D.5 (10in.)
- El Pajaro en jaula -- El Relicario, Los Piratas del Valle, Kingsville, TX., Canasta Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Piratas del Valle... El Pajaro en jaula -- El Relicario --; SWF 90.3/D.1 (7in.)
- La Muerte de Isaias -- El Besito que me diste, Los Piratas del Valle, Kingsville, TX., Canasta Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Piratas del Valle... La Muerte de Isaias -- El Besito que me diste --; SWF 90.3/D.2 (7in.)
- Contrabando de Nogales -- Yo no soy Nadie, Pino, Alberto, Kingsville, TX., Canasta Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 7 in.; Los Angeles, CA., Musimex Inc.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 7 in.; SWF 90.3/D.3 (7in.)
- Tu amor ha crecido grande -- Nunca nunca, De La Garza, Roy, Phoenix, AZ., Disque O Arte, p1980; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Roy De La Garza... Tu amor ha crecido grande -- Nunca nunca --; SWF 90.3/D.4 (7in.)
- La Guitarra y el mar -- Ocho dias, Los Hermanos Velez, 1976; Discos Cobra, p1976; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Hermanos Velez... La Guitarra y el mar -- Ocho dias --; SWF 90.3/D.5 (7in.)
- Que te vaya bonito -- Companera, Loza, Ramiro y Mariachi La Fuente, Tucson, AZ., RL Discos; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Ramiro Loza y Mariachi La Fuente... Que te vaya bonito -- Companera --; SWF 90.3/D.6 (7in.)
- Beso de un hijo -- Bonito lucero, Los Ultimos, Tucson, AZ., Copper State Recording Company, Inc.; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Ultimos... Beso de un hijo -- Bonito lucero --; SWF 90.3/D.7 (7in.)
- Confusion -- Con nada me pagas, Garcia, Pedro (Pete) y los Brilliantes, Mesa, AZ., Discos Soulo; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Pete Garcia y los Brilliantes... Vocals by Los Hermanos Sanchez... Confusion -- Con nada me pagas--; SWF 90.3/D.8 (7in.)
- La Voz varonil de Juan Fernando, Diochea, Juan Fernando, Mesa, AZ., Discos Solo and Tapes; 1 sound disc (4 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Juan Fernando Diochea... La Voz varonil de Juan Fernando -- Aburrido me voy -- Bebo --; SWF 90.3/D.9 (7in.)
- Falsas lagrimas -- Memoria a Jose Alfredo, Rodriguez, Enrique, Mesa, AZ., Discos Soulo; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Enrique Rodriguez... Falsas lagrimas -- Memoria a Jose Alfredo --; SWF 90.3/D.10 (7in.)
- Mi ultimo adios -- Para bien de los dos, Campos, Juan, Mesa, AZ., Discos Soulo; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Juan Campos... Accompanied by Lalo Mata y Los Llaneros... Mi ultimo adios -- Para bien de los dos --; SWF 90.3/D.11 (7in.)
- Mi pueblo es cananea -- Siempre viva, Oquita, Ramón con Mariachi, Mesa, AZ., Discos Soulo; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Ramon Oquita con Mariachi... Mi pueblo es cananea -- Siempre viva --; SWF 90.3/D.12 (7in.)
- Por elegancia -- Traicionera, Los Dinamitas del Norte, Mesa, AZ., Discos Soulo; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Dinamitas del Norte... Canta: Lupe Leyva... Por elegancia -- Traicionera --; SWF 90.3/D.13 (7in.)
- Despues de querernos tanto -- Tres barajas, Acosta, Julio con el Mariachi Colonial de Lupe Esparza, Avondale, AZ., Soulo Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Julio Acosta con el Mariachi Colonial de Lupe Esparza... Despues de querernos tanto -- Tres barajas --; SWF 90.3/D.14 (7in.)
- Migajas de amores -- Lautima palabra, Mariachi los 4 del colonial, Delray Beach, FL. Trevino Enterprises; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Mariachi los 4 del colonial... Migajas de amores -- Lautima palabra --; SWF 90.3/D.15 (7in.)
- Carino sincero -- Que vuelva conmigo, Sanchez, Louie con el Mariachi Colonial de Lupe Esparza, Avondale, AZ., Soulo Records; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Louie Sanchez con el Mariachi Colonial de Lupe Esparza... Carino sincero -- Que vuelva conmigo --; SWF 90.3/D.16 (7in.)
- Cuando vivas conmigo -- Que bonito amor, Jimenez, Miguel con el Mariachi Colonial de Lupe Esparza, Avondale, AZ., Soulo Records; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Miguel Jimenez con el Mariachi Colonial de Lupe Esparza -- Cuando vivas conmigo -- Que bonito amor --; SWF 90.3/D.17 (7in.)
- Corazon enbenenado -- Corrido a Bill Soltero, Los Madrugadores del Valle, Avondale, AZ., Soulo Records; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Madrugadores del Valle... Cantan: Ramon y Fermin... Corazon enbenenado -- Corrido a Bill Soltero --; SWF 90.3/D.18 (7in.)
- Imposible -- Siempre hace frio, Jimenez, Miguel con el Mariachi Colonial, Avondale, AZ., Soulo Records; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Miguel Jimenez con el Mariachi Colonial... Imposible -- Siempre hace frio --; SWF 90.3/D.19 (7in.)
- Si no te vas -- Pase la botella, Garcia, Pedro (Pete) y los Brillantes, Avondale, AZ., Soulo Records; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Pete Garcia y los Brillantes... Cantan: Ray, Billy y Pete... Si no te vas -- Pase la botella --; SWF 90.3/D.20 (7in.)
- Tu hazana, tu juego -- Cumbia - El Enredo, Grupo MonteCarlo, Mesa, AZ., Discos Solo; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Grupo MonteCarlo... Tu hazana, tu juego -- Cumbia - El Enredo --; SWF 90.3/D.21 (7in.)
- Memoria a Jose Alfredo -- Falsas lagrimas, Rodriguez, Enrique, Mesa, AZ., Discos Solo; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Enrique Rodriguez... Memoria a Jose Alfredo -- Falsas lagrimas --; SWF 90.3/D.22 (7in.)
- No te diran -- Engreido, Garcia, Pedro (Pete) y Jesus Armenta, Mesa, AZ., Discos Solo; 1 sound disc (4 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Pete Garcia y Jesus Armenta... No te diran -- Engreido --; SWF 90.3/D.23 (7in.)
- Perdona mi falsedad -- La Parida, Aurelio y sus Traviesos, Phoenix, AZ., El Capri; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Aurelio y sus Traviesos... Perdona mi falsedad -- La Parida --; SWF 90.3/D.24 (7in.)
- La Lucha -- Como esos amantes, Hnos [Hermanos] Vega, 1985; Phoenix, AZ., Marquez Records, [1985]; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Hermanos Vega... La Lucha -- Como esos amantes --; SWF 90.3/D.25 (7in.)
- Paloma -- El Fraca so de el alambaista, Sensacion, 1982; Phoenix, AZ., Sensamar, [1982]; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Sensacion... Paloma -- El Fraca so de el alambaista --; SWF 90.3/D.26 (7in.)
- Te faltan alas -- El Chasco, Los Indolos de Mexicali, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Mayra; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Indolos de Mexicali... Te faltan alas -- El Chasco --; SWF 90.3/D.27 (7in.)
- El Corrido de los mojados -- Estamos a mano, Pino, Alberto, Phoenix, AZ., Discos A.R.P.A. [ARPA] (Arizona Record Production Association); 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Alberto Pina... El Corrido de los mojados -- Estamos a mano --; SWF 90.3/D.28 (7in.)
- El Gran momento -- Es as del contrabando, Pino, Alberto, Phoenix, AZ., ARPA Records [Arizona Record Production Association]; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Alberto Pina... El Gran momento -- Es as del contrabando --; SWF 90.3/D.29 (7in.)
- Cosas que suceden -- Goviotas, Pino, Alberto, Phoenix, AZ., ARPA Records [Arizona Record Production Association]; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Alberto Pina... Cosas que suceden -- Goviotas --; SWF 90.3/D.30 (7in.)
- Llorando y cantando -- Quisiera que pudieras, Pino, Alberto, Phoenix, AZ., ARPA Records [Arizona Record Production Association]; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Alberto Pina... Llorando y cantando -- Quisiera que pudieras --; SWF 90.3/D.31 (7in.)
- Roses in December -- Si tu te vas, Pino, Alberto, Phoenix, AZ., ARPA Records [Arizona Record Production Association]; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Alberto Pina... Roses in December -- Si tu te vas --; SWF 90.3/D.32 (7in.)
- Cada quien su camino -- Cuando caigan las hojas, Grupo Jano's, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Mayra; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Grupo Jano's... Cada quien su camino -- Cuando caigan las hojas --; SWF 90.3/D.33 (7in.)
- Porque sera -- Blanca, Los Dorados de Torreon, El Dorado Discos; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Dorados de Torreon... Porque sera -- Blanca --; SWF 90.3/D.34 (7in.)
- Las Copas y ella -- Tratando de olvidar, Jinuez, Gabriel, Gilbert, AZ., Discos Excelentes; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Gabriel Jinuez... Las Copas y ella -- Tratando de olvidar --; SWF 90.3/D.35 (7in.)
- Esta noche corazon -- Que lindo Las Cruces, Marka-Miramontes, Inez and Manuel Marka-Miramontes, Gilbert, AZ., Discos Excelentes; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Manuel and Inez Marka-Miramontes... Esta noche corazon -- Que lindo Las Cruces --; SWF 90.3/D.36 (7in.)
- El Barco loco -- La Paciada, Valenzuela, Ricardo, Discos RUF; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Ricardo Valenzuela... El Barco loco - Corrido de Jesus Armienta -- La Paciada --; SWF 90.3/D.37 (7in.)
- Linda Morena -- Corrido de Juan Villanueva, Valenzuela, Richard con Los Catanes de la Frontera, Discos RUF; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Richard Valenzuela con Los Catanes de la Frontera... Linda Morena -- Corrido de Juan Villanueva --; SWF 90.3/D.38 (7in.)
- Presiento tu traicion -- Te encontrare, Los Piratas del Valle, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Mayra; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Piratas del Valle... Presiento tu traicion -- Te encontrare --; SWF 90.3/D.39 (7in.)
- Mar de penas -- Ya me voy pa' California, Mata, Lalo y Sus Llaneros, Phoenix, AZ., La Cita Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Lalo Mato y Sus Llaneros... Mar de penas -- Ya me voy pa' California --; SWF 90.3/D.40 (7in.)
- Dos cruzes -- Rosario de mi madre, Luna, Aquiles, Phoenix, AZ., Luna Discos; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Aquiles Luna... Dos cruzes -- Rosario de mi madre --; SWF 90.3/D.41 (7in.)
- Music and perfume -- Copitao de nieve, Heenan, Bill, 1982; Phoenix, AZ., Mirasol Music Co., p1982; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Aquiles Luna... Dos cruzes -- Rosario de mi madre --; SWF 90.3/D.42 (7in.)
- Eres mi sol -- Los Lechujeros, Reyes, Ramon y Los Haneros de Lalo Mata, Phoenix, AZ., Pantera Record Co., 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Ramon Reyes y Los Haneros de Lalo Mata... Eres mi sol -- Los Lechujeros --; SWF 90.3/D.43 (7in.)
- Corrido de los rehenes -- El Bandoler, Lopez, Ramon y Roberto, Phoenix, AZ., Pantera Record Co., 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by El Dueto Los Bandoleros: Ramon y Roberto Lopez... Corrido de los rehenes -- El Bandoler --; SWF 90.3/D.44 (7in.)
- Versos de un mojado -- El Corrido de casas grandes, Carbajal, Javier and Ramon Lopez y Roberto Lopez, Phoenix, AZ., Pantera Record Co., 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Versos de un mojado (Javier Carbajal) -- El Corrido de casas grandes (El Duetos los Bandoleros: Ramon Lopez y Roberto Lopez) --; SWF 90.3/D.45 (7in.)
- Va para ti -- La Media caida, Los Rivales, Flagstaff, AZ., Rivales Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Rivales... Va para ti -- La Media caida --; SWF 90.3/D.46 (7in.)
- El Momento -- Entre copa y copa, Los Rivales, Flagstaff, AZ., Rivales Records; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Rivales... El Momento -- Entre copa y copa --; SWF 90.3/D.47 (7in.)
- Mi promesa -- Geraldo Rosas, Los Marinos de Johnny Ortiz, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Azteca de Phoenix; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Marinos de Johnny Ortiz... Mi promesa -- Geraldo Rosas --; SWF 90.3/D.48 (7in.)
- De vuelve de dinero -- La Chapucera, Tropical Moderno, Discos VAS Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Tropical Moderno... De vuelve de dinero -- La Chapucera --; SWF 90.3/D.49 (7in.)
- Las Gaviotas -- La Otra, Amaya, Gloria Ramona, Discos VAS Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Gloria Ramona... With Mariachi Los Charros de Ameca de Ramon Palovar... Las Gaviotas -- La Otra --; SWF 90.3/D.50 (7in.)
- Tu negro camino -- Envidia, Cota, Enrique, Discos VAS Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Enrique Cota... With Mariachi Los Charros de Ameca de Ramon Palovar... Tu negro camino -- Envidia --; SWF 90.3/D.51 (7in.)
- Tu vendras a quererme mas -- Quise, quise matarte, Hinojosa, Luis R., Discos VAS Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Luis R. Hinojosa... With Mariachi Los Charros de Ameca de Ramon Palovar... Tu vendras a quererme mas -- Quise, quise matarte --; SWF 90.3/D.52 (7in.)
- Despojos -- El Florero de bolitas, Los Espejos, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Pajarito; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Espejos... Despojos -- El Florero de bolitas --; SWF 90.3/D.53 (7in.)
- Ta Jitanita -- Mis brasos te esperan, Los Gorriones Norteñios, Phoenix, AZ., Del Pajarito Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Gorriones Norteñios... Ta Jitanita -- Mis brasos te esperan --; SWF 90.3/D.54 (7in.)
- La Rubia and la morena -- Alsa esos ojos y mirame, Los Gorriones Homero y Jose, Phoenix, AZ., Del Pajarito Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Gorriones Homero y Jose... La Rubia and la morena -- Alsa esos ojos y mirame --; SWF 90.3/D.55 (7in.)
- Me ha tocado perder -- La Mosca, Los Espejos, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Pajarito; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Los Espejos... Me ha tocado perder -- La Mosca --; SWF 90.3/D.56 (7in.)
- Menudita -- Soy del arbol wayacan, Los Aquilas de Pedro Montelongo, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Pajarito; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Aquilas de Pedro Montelongo... Menudita -- Soy del arbol wayacan de Simon Barrientos --; SWF 90.3/D.57 (7in.)
- Cielo de sonora -- El Corrido de Hector M. Garcia, Garcia, Victoria M., con Los Gorriones de Homero y Jose, Phoenix, AZ., Del Parjarito Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Victoria M. Garcia con Los Gorriones de Homero y Jose...Cielo de sonora -- El Corrido de Hector M. Garcia --; SWF 90.3/D.58 (7in.)
- El Arrugado -- La Flor que no comprendi, Los Dinamicos de Reynosa, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Pajarito; 1 sound disc (5 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Dinamicos de Reynosa... El Arrugado -- La Flor que no comprendi --; SWF 90.3/D.59 (7in.)
- La Cuna vacia -- Me estoy acostumbrando, Los Piratas de Valle, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Pajarito; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Piratas de Valle... La Cuna vacia -- Me estoy acostumbrando --; SWF 90.3/D.60 (7in.)
- Yo no sabia -- El Cerillaso, Los Espejos, Phoenix, AZ., Discos Pajarito; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Los Espejos... Yo no sabia -- El Cerillaso --; SWF 90.3/D.61 (7in.)